Guide to the William R. George family papers, 1750-1989.
George, William R. family papers, 1750-1989.
- Series V. Printed Material
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. II, May 1912-Mar. 1913 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. III, Apr. 1913-Mar. 1914 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. IV, May 1914-Mar. 1915 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. V., Sept. 1915-Mar. 1916 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. VI, Apr. 1916-Mar. 1917 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. VII. - VIII, July 1917-Nov. 1918 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. IX, July 1919-Apr. 1920 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. X., Aug. 1920-June 1921 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XI, Jan. 1922-Dec. 1922 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XII, Jan. 1923-Dec. 1923 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XIII, Jan. 1924-Dec. 1924 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XIV, Feb. 1925-Dec. 1925 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XV, Jan. 1926-Dec. 1926 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XVI, Jan. 1927-Nov. 1927 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XVII, Jan. 1928-Oct. 1928 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XVIII, Jan. 1929-May 1929 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XIX - XXI, Jan. 1930-May 1932 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Junior Republic - serial publication of California Junior Republic, vol. XXIII - XXXI, July 1934-May 1942 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Connecticut Junior Republic - miscellaneous printed material, 1921-1975, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of Connecticut Junior Republic, vols. I & II, Apr. 1916-Nov. 1917 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of Connecticut Junior Republic, vols. III & IV, June 1918-Feb. 1922 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of Connecticut Junior Republic, Apr. 1922-Dec. 1924 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of Connecticut Junior Republic, 1925-1927 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - The Junior Citizen., 1932-1963 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - The Junior Citizen, vols. 39-43., 1971-1975 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - The Junior Citizen, vols. 44-48., 1976-1979 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Maryland Junior Republic (National Junior Republic) - miscellaneous printed material, 1912-1913, n.d. (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - National (Maryland) Junior Republic Annual Reports, 1913-1917 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - The National Junior Republic News - serial publication of Maryland Junior Republic, 1911-1912 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - The Republic News., 1913 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - The Republic News., 1914 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - The Republic News., 1915 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - The Republic News., 1916-1917 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - New Jersey Junior Republic - miscellaneous printed material, 1912-1922, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - W. T. Carter Junior Republic (Pennsylvania) - miscellaneous printed material, 1912 (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Pennsylvania Junior Republic, Grove City, - miscellaneous printed material, 1910-1985, n.d. (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - The Pioneer Citizen - serial publication of Pennsylvania Junior Republic, 1910 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - The Pioneer Citizen - serial publication of Pennsylvania Junior Republic, 1911-June 1912 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - The Pioneer Citizen - serial publication of Pennsylvania Junior Republic, July 1912-Dec. 1912 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - The Pioneer Citizen - serial publication of Pennsylvania Junior Republic, 1913 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Boys Brotherhood Republic of New York - miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - The Junior Republic Messenger - serial publication of Pennsylvania Junior Republic, 1946-1948 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Washington Junior Republic - miscellaneous printed material, 1910-1915 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Other republics - printed material, 1901-1947, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Related topics; youth, social welfare, etc., 1912-1941 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Related topics; youth, social welfare etc., 1942-1976, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Related topics; youth, education, 1911-1961, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Related topics, 1902-1962, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 7)
  - Related topics; child labor amendment, 1924-1935 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Related topics; child labor amendment, n.d. (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1895-1897 (Box 102, Folder 1)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1898-1899 (Box 102, Folder 2)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1900-1901 (Box 102, Folder 3)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1902-1910 (Box 102, Folder 4)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1911-1915 (Box 102, Folder 5)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1916-1920 (Box 102, Folder 6)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1921-1925 (Box 102, Folder 7)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1926-1933 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1934-1935 (Box 102, Folder 9)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1936-1945 (Box 103, Folder 1)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1946-1954 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., 1955-1983 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Magazine articles about G.J.R. or W.R.G., n.d. (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. A-B, n.d. (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. C-D., n.d. (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. E-F., n.d. (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. G., n.d. (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. H-J., n.d. (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. K., n.d. (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. L-Q., n.d. (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. R-S., n.d. (Box 104, Folder 2)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. T-U., n.d. (Box 104, Folder 3)
  - Printed material mentioning friends, relatives, ex-citizens, etc. V-Z., n.d. (Box 104, Folder 4)
  - New York State Association of Student Councils, and Tri-State Student Council, 1949-1960 (Box 104, Folder 5)
  - Fragments and miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 6)
  - Fragments and miscellaneous, n.d. (Box 104, Folder 7)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. I, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1898-July 1899 (Box 104, Folder 8)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. II, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1899-July 1900 (Box 104, Folder 9)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. III, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1900-July 1901 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. IV, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1901-July 1902 (Box 105, Folder 1)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. V, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1902-July 1903 (Box 105, Folder 2)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. VI, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1903-July 1904 (Box 105, Folder 3)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. VII, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1904-July 1905 (Box 105, Folder 4)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. VIII, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1905-July 1905 (Box 105, Folder 5)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. IX, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1906-July 1907 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. X, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1907-July 1908 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. XI, nos. 1-12., Aug. 1908-July 1909 (Box 105, Folder 8)
  - Junior Republic Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., vol. XII, nos. 1-5., Aug. 1909-Dec. 1909 (Box 105, Folder 9)
  - The Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., 1910 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - The Citizen - serial publication of G.J.R., 1911 (Box 105, Folder 11)
  - The Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1912 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - The Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1913 (Box 106, Folder 2)
  - The Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1914 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - The Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1915 (Box 106, Folder 4)
  - The Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1916 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1925 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1926 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1927 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1933, 1936 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1938 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1939 (Box 106, Folder 11)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1940 (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, 1941 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, Mar. 1942 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, Oct. 1945 (Box 107, Folder 3)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial, Dec. 1946 (Box 107, Folder 4)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial; vol. I, nos. 1-12., 1950 (Box 107, Folder 5)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial; vol. I, nos. 13-26., 1951 (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial; vol. I, nos. 27-33., 1952 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial; vol. I, nos. 34-37., 1953 (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial; vol. II, nos. 1-21., Nov. 1956-Nov. 1957 (Box 107, Folder 9)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial; vol. III, nos. 1-20., Nov. 1957-Nov. 1958 (Box 107, Folder 10)
  - The Junior Citizen - G.J.R. serial; vol. IV, nos. 1-5., Nov. 1958-Feb. 1959 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - The Junior Citizen Magazine - G.J.R. quarterly, name changed to Junior Republic Citizen., 1967-1971 (Box 107, Folder 12)
  - Nothing Without Labor - G.J.R. annual, 1894-1945 (Box 107, Folder 13)
  - Citizens in the Making - G.J.R. annual, 1925-1935 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Rotary Notice., 1921-1932 (Box 107, Folder 15)
  - Altoona Beam, Boys Club News, The Hunter., 1938-1950 (Box 107, Folder 16)
  - The East & West Association, The Buck an' a Quarter., 1944-1946 (Box 107, Folder 17)
  - The Daily News - G.J.R., 1915-1916 (Box 107, Folder 18)
  - The Republican of the GJR., 1922 (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Venture '77 - G.J.R., 1977 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - The Advocate of the GJR, vol. I, nos. 1-21., 1922-1923 (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - The Advocate of the GJR, vol. I, nos. 22-38., 1924-1925 (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Republic Tattler - G.J.R., 1931 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - GJR Personnel Management News Dispatch., ca. 1930-1933 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - The Republic Scribe - G.J.R., 1934 (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Shop Talk - G.J.R., 1939 (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - The Junior Republic Weekly News-Letter -G.J.R., 1940 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - The Snoopier Citizen, vol. I, nos. 1-12 - G.J.R., 1941 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - The Citizen - G.J.R., 1942 (Box 108, Folder 9)
  - The Republic Chronicle - G.J.R., 1947 (Box 108, Folder 10)
  - The Citizen News - G.J.R., 1948-1949 (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - ??? - G.J.R., 1935-1950 (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - GJR Alumni News., 1947-1982 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - The Citizen Reporter - G.J.R., 1960 (Box 108, Folder 14)
  - Letter from the Junior Republic - G.J.R., 1961 (Box 108, Folder 15)
  - Group B in Living Black and White - G.J.R., 1961 (Box 108, Folder 16)
  - The GJR Newsletter., 1962 (Box 108, Folder 17)
  - GJR Community Bulletin., 1963 (Box 108, Folder 18)
  - G.J.R. Association printed material, 1895-1982 (Box 108, Folder 19)
  - Community Education., 1963-1965 (Box 108, Folder 20)
  - The Town Crier - G.J.R., 1967-1968 (Box 108, Folder 21)
  - Alexander's Gazette., 1968 (Box 108, Folder 22)
  - Crossroads - G.J.R., 1968 (Box 108, Folder 23)
  - The GJR Bulletin., 1969-1971 (Box 108, Folder 24)
  - The GJR Bulletin., 1972-1973 (Box 108, Folder 25)
  - GJR News., 1969-1973 (Box 108, Folder 26)
  - The Chronicle - G.J.R., 1973 (Box 108, Folder 27)
  - GJR Calendar., 1978-1982 (Box 108, Folder 28)
  - GJR Times., 1979-1980 (Box 108, Folder 29)
  - GJR Times., 1981-1983 (Box 108, Folder 30)
  - Books by W.R.G.
    - The Junior Republic., 1910 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - The Adult Minor., 1912 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - The "Self-Government as a Means of Moral Education" in Proceedings of the Second International Moral Education Congress, 1912 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - "The Work of the Institution in the Reformation of Delinquent Boys" in Addresses Delivered Before The Canadian Club of Montreal., 1912-1913 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Citizens Made and Remade, with L. B. Stowe, 1937 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Books about G.J.R.
    - Report of the Reformatory Section (National Conference of Charities and Corrections)., 1901 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Dan, A Citizen of a Junior Republic (I. T. Thurston)., 1901 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Institutional Life (A. J. Pillsbury)., 1906 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - The New State: Group Organization the Solution of Popular Government (M. P. Follett)., 1920 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Heredity (A. E. Winship)., 1925 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - A Laboratory Study in Democracy (E. D. Bruner)., 1927 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - The Dangerous Life (B. B. Lindsey & R. Borough)., 1931 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - Constitution & General Laws of the GJR (C. T. Burns, R. M. Christy, A. A. Cusco, D. R. Lakin, W. B. Luce, M. M. Rumsey), 1936 (Box 110, Folder 8)
    - The New Pioneers (V. C. Rockwell)., 1940 (Box 110, Folder 9-10)
    - As the Twig is Bent (R. Welling)., 1942 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - East Side Story (W. Welling)., 1982 (Box 110, Folder 12)
  - Books used at G.J.R.
    - A Ten Year's War (J. A. Riis)., 1900 (Box 111, Folder 1)
    - A Manual of Devotion (H. C. Potter, E. G. Andrews, C. C. Hall, W. H. P. Faunce)., 1904 (Box 111, Folder 2)
    - Course of Study for the Elementary Schools of the City of New York (Board of Education)., 1905 (Box 111, Folder 3)
    - Football for Players and Coaches., 1912 (Box 111, Folder 4)
    - Kriemhild Herd: A Chapter in Holstein History (F. N. Decker)., 1923 (Box 111, Folder 5)
    - Constitution and General Laws of the G.J.R. (C. T. Burns et at)., 1936 (Box 111, Folder 6-7)
- Series VI. Blueprints, Plans, and Certificates
  - Blueprints for "Proposed Bungalow for Mr. J. F. George" (2)., 1915 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Blueprints for "Alteration to Residence for William R. George" (3)., 1915 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Plan for "Mrs. Daddy's Park" by M. J. Freeborn (3 copies)., n.d. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Diploma of Esther I. Brewster from Normal College of the City of New York, 1890 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Large mounted testimonial to William R. George, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Diploma of Charles Carroll Moore from Hunt Memorial School of G.J.R., 1911 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Plan of the "First Class Accommodation" for R.M.S. "Adriatic.", ca. 1922 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "Saloon Plan" for "Berengaria.", ca. 1922 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Marriage certificate for William R. George and Esther I. Brewster, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Photocopy of annotated slip with 7 drawings of house owned by Kate Fowler, 1911 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Certificate of invitation to Mr. and Mrs. William R. George for Panama Pacific International Exposition, from California Development Board, 1915 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Large birthday greeting to Esther George from G.J.R. citizens, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Mounted annotated pencil drawing of Mrs. Daddy's Park, by M. J. Freeborn, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Mounted annotated photograph of three boys at G.J.R., ca. 1900 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mounted annotated photograph of boys and helper at G.J.R., ca. 1901-1902 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Freeborn genealogy charts (2)., n.d. (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Series VII. Museum Items
  - George Family Museum Items
    - Metal button inscribed "William F. Miller Library Assistant Librarian"; silver cross inscribed "IHN" (front) and "1886" (reverse) - belonged to Esther George from King's Daughters Society, Methodist Church, New York City, 1886 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - G.J.R. 45th anniversary button with picture of William R. George and two ribbons; G.J.R. pin of Edith Freeborn, ca. early 1900's, inscribed on reverse "E.V. George/Freeville, N.Y.", n.d. (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - Small metal badge/button "Crusade for Freedom"; small button with flag decoration; Rotary International lapel button of William R. George; New York State National Guard 22nd Regimental pin of William R. George; New York State Association of Student Councils pin of M.J. Freeborn, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - Small unpainted metal doll; Rotary International lapel button of M.J. Freeborn; USAF Ground Observer Corps service pin of Edith George (her assignment was atop Cornell University's Plant Science building); Edith George's American Red Cross service pin for volunteer duty in the Blood Program throughout Tompkins County, New York; Daughters of the American Revolution pin of Edith G. Freeborn; Delta Tau Delta "sister pin" given by M.J. Freeborn to Edith George - June 1929., 1929 (Box 112, Folder 4)
    - Rotary International badge with ribbon of William R. George; two badges with ribbons - Esther George - 1925 Rotary Convention - Cleveland, 1925 (Box 112, Folder 5)
    - Small porcelain doll in glass bottle, n.d. (Box 112, Folder 6)
    - Bone article (?)., n.d. (Box 112, Folder 7)
    - Head from porcelain doll; "lucky" penny from wallet of Esther George., n.d. (Box 112, Folder 8)
    - Small replica of pistol - belonged to William R. George; small brass bucket on pink ribbon; small woven reed box; silver thimble of Margaret Van Etten Baker (grandmother of William R. George)., n.d. (Box 112, Folder 9)
    - Wedding ring of "Grandmother Brewster"; rectangular agate in metal setting; small bracelet given by Edith G. Freeborn to Esther George; gold baby locket of Edith George inscribed "Evan E G.", n.d. (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - Political medallion - McKinley (?) - with ribbon; two Harrison political buttons from 1888., 1888 (Box 112, Folder 11)
    - Glass bottle containing dried flowers given by William C. Seidell to Eleanor B. George, 1897., 1897 (Box 112, Folder 12)
    - Three penknives - one belonging to William R. George but inscribed with name of "B.H. Vergne"; one in leather case given to Esther George by William R. George; one given to M.J. Freeborn by Edith G. Freeborn, Christmas 1929., 1929 (Box 112, Folder 13)
    - Woven reed box with 4 small boxes inside; small wood and straw replica of broom; wooden implement; 8 jewelry boxes made by William R. George in early business; gold and white pen in black case given by William R. George to Esther George; pencil inscribed "Mrs. Daddy"; gold mechanical pencil given by Esther George to William R. George "in later years"; flowered pen belonging to a grandmother of Edith G. Freeborn, n.d. (Box 112, Folder --)
    - Photocopy of check written to G.J.R. Association; mottos embroidered by Esther A.T. Brewster; motto kept in Bible of Esther George, n.d. (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - Ordination certificate for James Kelsey, with typed copy; Masonic Directory of the City of Troy; Rotary International; membership card for William R. George; military shooting record cards of William R. George; postal stamp on annotated cardboard marked by William R. George as "First parcel post stamp I ever saw"; book of G.J.R. bus tokens, 1810-1925 (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Ribbon badges from G.J.R. Founders Day, New York State Association of Secondary School Administrators, and New York State Sunday School Convention; name badge for M.J. Freeborn from New York State Association of Secondary School Administrators Conference, 1894-1962 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Ribbon badges from McKinley and Hobart, the Good Government Party, Wholesale Dry Goods Harrison and Morton Club, and Republic Volunteer Association, 1889-1896 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - Card and ribbon badges from Young People's Society of Christian Endeavor (8)., 1890-1892 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - Ribbon badges - "Captain" and "Floor"; hand painted ribbon marked "Easter Memories"; printed bookmark marked "Mizpah.", 1886 (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Hunt Memorial School diploma for Charles B. Dawson; Teaching Assistant License for Esther I. Brewster; Daughters of the American Revolution certificate for Esther George; G.J.R. Boy Scout Troop charter; two luggage tags and bus map of London belonging to William R. George, 1894-1939 (Box 113, Folder --)
    - Annotated envelopes from insignia (not in collection) sent to Esther George, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
    - Military insignia, Cpl. Bill Kirkland, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 3)
    - Military insignia, Sgt. Walter P. Bogatis, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 4)
    - Military insignia, unidentified, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 5)
    - Military insignia, Paul McGarrigle, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 6)
    - Military insignia, Warren Ungermah, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 7)
    - Military insignia, Johann Stawinski, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - Military insignia, Walter Bogatis, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - Military insignia, Edward I. Hardy, July 1946 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - Belgian 10 franc note from Johann Stawinski, Nov. 1944 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Japanese 1 peso note from Don Brunet, May 1945 (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - French 5 franc notes from Edward Hardy (2)., July 1944 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Chinese 5 yuan note and Japanese half-rupee and 1 rupee notes from Robert Rogers, May 1945 (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - German 1934 5 mark coin and Belgian 70c postal stamp from Johann Stawinski, May 1945 (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Chinese 1 dollar note from Don Brunel, Nov. 1945 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - German 1942 penny from Johann Stawinski, Feb. 1945 (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Two Japanese 1 yen notes and 2 Japanese 50 sen notes from Eddie Craig, Oct. 1945 (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Surrender and Safe Conduct pass dropped on German forces, from Ed Comicko, Feb. 1945 (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Russian 1 kopeka coin sent from Germany by Johann Stawinski, June 1945 (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Small piece of U.S. Cub Plane shot down by Americans to keep Germans from having it, from Johann Stawinski, Feb. 1945 (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - German postage stamps (4); emblem worn on the sleeve of Ukrainian refugees in Germany, marking the wearer "as a pig," from Johann Stawinski, Apr. 1945 (Box 114, Folder 22)
    - U.S. Marine Corps pin given by Freeman Brewster to Edith George (World War I)., n.d. (Box 114, Folder 23)
    - World War II pins given to Edith Freeborn by "boys" from Susquehanna Valley Home in Binghamton, New York, n.d. (Box 114, Folder 24-25)
    - One flag (with stand) of G.J.R., given to Esther George in 1954; flag made by Esther A. Brewster in 1860; "Jap Navy Flag" brought from Guadalcanal by Paul Bielac as souvenir for G.J.R.; U.S. flag, 1860-1954 (Box 114, Folder --)